[Music]
Tell me, daughter-in-law, go to school and see
Hey Sabani brother, I don't know, listen, Pila is a fool,
two, from that, who is a
fool, Pila goes to school all the time,
tuitions are also given, and Pila is a fool, even after
studying in a government school,
look at me, he goes to a private school, he studies only in
English, and you Pila is a fool
[Music]
Hey, listen, Pila, what is a private school,
write down your progress, study in a
village school,
study in a private school
[Laughter] If I
know, then don't take it, you will get it, it will give you the
future
[Music]
also, take
admission in an English medium private school
[Music]
[Encouraging voice] [
Music]
[Music]
Hey old lady, give me enthusiasm,
brother,
look at
everyone
[Music]
Hey, take the
complete
[Music]
Write the details, look at the
school,
one,
Pila, up
school, get the school, cancel
[Music]
Khariya
school, school,
get it,
okay sir, take admission today itself,
okay sir, I have to deposit 25000 in the counter,
sir  25000
you na 500 hey aunty's future
[Music]
hey go to school quickly go to
school quickly go lying down
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
hey Gitu you should also write in the new school
good school full marble Chakchakki
hey khali taku ko to sab bhi study in the new school have
fun [Laughs]
no uncle go to
school re bha
private school ko sun se khemi
roll ice cream sab mil mo tu bhi
moba nahi mo school mo be paste to ja
pani dali kha kalu to hum
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music]
Natiya school khata dhar ke basi pad to wash hands do
khab
khamwork de
khabi
kaun karo sorry
sir sorry
you have to
give homework
you should go and write the homework
tell me bahu ma said
tomorrow school
said
yes hello ma eh ko to buni to
pura school to sab parli eh to ko bhi bujh ho nahi to padh de buni
[Music] listen
school lesson bujh par nahi mu padh pub nhi hey
Teach me, oh
aunty, do
n't educate anyone in private school, I will
also educate you in the right manner, pay 1000 rupees
home tax,
oh baba, you should take me to school,
papa, take me to school,
today the school fee, coaching fee,
who will be able to pay 25000 rupees, admission is
going on
[groaning sound] [screaming sound],
oh you help me, you can take the school, you can take the basic
[laughter],
school fee, coaching fee, all the fees, you can take the
school, you can
write and enter the
admission, all the fees, go to
the
private school,
[laughter],
ok,
educate me in private school,
oh jotiya basi, you have to
forget
private school, it is a
big
empty taka,
oh vidya samaj adhikariyan,
quickly go to your class
[music]
baba, you understand,
sorry, school, fail, school, you mean, oh
fool, fail, then pass, school, school, school
[laughter],
dada
[music]
we
these